http://www.jensenprecast.com/privacy/

Product Categories
Access Hatches & CoversView AllAluminum Access HatchesLockLid High Security Utility CoversSteel Access HatchesTraxplate Slip Resistant SurfaceUtility Agency Specifications AgriculturalView AllBunker SilosCattle GuardsFeed BunksT-PanelsWater Trough Box CulvertsView AllMonolithicSegmental Box Culvert Buildings & Shelters Concrete Fence Drainage Inlets & Catch BasinsView AllCaltrans InletsCurb InletsDrop Inlets Earth Retention SystemsView AllBig Block Retaining WallsGravix Retaining Walls Redi-Rock Retaining Walls Electric Utility StructuresView AllAccessoriesEquipment EnclosuresHandholesLight Pole BasesManholesManholes/VaultsPadsPull/Splice BoxesTrenchesVaults Highway BarrierView AllAccessoriesBarrier RailCaltrans Temporary Railing (Type K) Interceptors & SeparatorsView AllAccessoriesClarifiersCoalescing Oil Water SeparatorsGravity Grease InterceptorsProduct Specifications and InformationSample BoxesSand TrapsSand-Oil InterceptorsSpecial ApplicationsTypical Applications Irrigation Water Control Natural Gas Utility StructuresView AllAccessoriesHandholesPull/Splice BoxesValve BoxesVaultsWater BoxesWater Meter Vaults Pump Stations Reinforced Concrete PipeView AllConcrete PipeHeadwalls Septic & Wastewater SystemsView AllCommercial Septic TanksOnsite Wastewater TreatmentResidential Septic Tanks Sewer & Storm Drain ManholesView AllAccessoriesDrainage TrenchManholes Stormwater SystemsView AllCoalescing InterceptorsJensen Stormwater Systems WebsiteJPHV InterceptorsRain Water Collection Systems Telecom Utility StructuresView AllAccessoriesHandholesManholesPadsPull/Splice Boxes TransportationView AllBoat Ramp PlanksParking Curbs Underground EnclosuresView AllBrooksElectric Utility BoxesPlastic Utility and Valve BoxesPolymer ConcreteTraffic BoxesTraffic Valve BoxesWater Meter Boxes Universal ApplicationsView AllAccessoriesBoxesHolding TanksManholesManholes/VaultsPanel VaultsPull/Splice Boxes
Privacy
California Residents
If you reside in California, you have the right to ask us one time each year if we have shared personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes as well as to opt out of the sale of your Personal Information.
To make a request please submit an inquiry to the following address: Jensen Enterprises, Inc. dba Jensen Precast 825 Steneri way, Sparks, NV 89431. In your request, please specify that you want a "Your California CCPA Information." Please allow 30 days for a response.
You may also request such information at privacy@jensenprecast.com.
California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) of 2018. Effective January 1, 2020, if you reside in California then you have the following rights:
You have the right to opt-out of sale of your Personal Information.
You have the right to request the deletion of your Personal Information.
You have the right to request us to disclose to you the following, no more than twice in a 12-month period:
Categories of Personal Information we collected about you during the preceding 12 months.
Categories of sources from which we collected the Personal Information during the preceding 12 months.
Business or commercial purpose(s) for collecting or selling your Personal Information during the preceding 12 months.
Categories of third parties with whom we share the Personal Information during the preceding 12 months.
Specific pieces of Personal Information we collected about you during the preceding 12 months.
Categories of Personal Information we have sold and categories of third parties to whom the information was sold to during the preceding 12 months.
Categories of Personal Information we disclosed about you for a business purpose during the preceding 12 months.
We will not discriminate against you because you exercised your rights under this section of our Notice.
For purposes of exercising your rights above, please note the following regarding how we collect and use your Personal Information as described in this Notice:
We collect the following categories of personal information: Identifiers; payment information; commercial information; internet of other electronic network activity information; geolocation data; audio, electronic or visual information.
We disclose the following categories of personal information for a business purpose: Identifiers; payment information; commercial information; device information; demographic information and driver’s license number.
Based on the definition of “sell” under the CCPA and under current regulatory guidance, we do not believe we engage in such activity and have not engaged in such activity in the past twelve months (including that we do not “sell” the personal information of minors under 16 years of age).
If would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us via email or written request:
Email: privacy@jensenprecast.com
Jensen Enterprises, Inc. dba Jensen Precast
Attn: CCPA Request
9895 Double R Blvd
Reno, NV 89521
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. We also use cookies to assist in our marketing and data analysis. To learn more, view our Privacy Policy.By continuing to use this site, or closing this box, you consent to the use of cookies. Accept
